# Tania Papazafeiropoulou - Curriculum vitae

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

- Hendon, London, NW4 (United Kingdom)
- Mello@tany4.com
- tany4.com
- www.linkedin.com/in/taniapapazaf
- 1 http://stackoverflow.com/story/tany4
- www.github.com/altany

#### PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am a Full Stack Web Developer with a real passion for Front-End. I love creating user friendly web apps and particularly enjoy working with Node.js, React, Javascript, Sass, etc. Lately, I have been working with React Native and exploring TDD using tools like Mocha. I thrive in close knit teams and find collaborating and sharing knowledge necessary for a successful and fulfilling programming experience.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### March 2016 - Present

## Web Developer

Cult Beauty, London (United Kingdom)

Currently working on transforming Cult Beauty to an established online retailer. Using everything JavaScript to handle scale and -of course- write cool features! Some of my most enjoyable technologies include ReactJS, Node.js, Selenium (WebdriverIO) and SASS.

#### June 2014 - February 2016

#### Web Developer

IDG UK, London (United Kingdom)

IDG UK is a digital publisher company and my role included maintaining, improving and extending the current websites, including PC Advisor, Macworld, ComputerWorld, Digital Arts Online and TechWorld. Additionally, I created bespoke microsites and worked within specialised teams to rebuild websites from scratch. The technologies and frameworks I used daily were:

- Coldfusion
- JavaScript
- jQuery
- SASS / SCSS
- RequireJS

As a direct result of my work, revenue and traffic across all core IDG Websites were significantly increased.

# December 2013 – February 2014

# **Website Developer**

Up Skill 4 Life Ltd, London (United Kingdom)

I was responsible for planning, developing, testing and delivering the company's website. The technologies used were HTML5, PHP, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery and AJAX.

Website URL: http://www.upskill4life.com

8/12/16 Page 1 / 3

# Tania Papazafeiropoulou - Curriculum vitae

## January 2013 - June 2014

### **Software Developer**

Kantar Worldpanel, London (United Kingdom)

Took ownership of small projects, produced system and user documentation and trained other developers, all in a fast paced environment. Most of my projects were implemented using PHP, MySQL/MS SQL, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery and Ajax. Additionally, I regularly designed Office plugins in VBA.

During my employment, I proposed, designed and implemented automations to processes involving hundreds of employees. Two of my most interesting contributions were a reporting tool that automated archaic processes and an internal dashboard that assisted users by visualising relevant data in real time. As a result, the company experienced a significant increase in productivity in my areas of involvement.

## September 2010 - July 2011

# **Computer Lab Assistant**

**TechnoPlus** 

Kiprou 38, 26441 Patras (Greece)

My major tasks were providing support and guidance to students throughout the learning process, in the fields of web page design, image/video editing and advanced computer usage concepts. Furthermore, I provided secretarial support and updated/maintained the company's website.

# February 2008 – June 2008

#### **Assembly Lab Assistant**

University Of Patras, Patras (Greece)

Supervising and guiding the students through advanced Assembly projects.

#### **EDUCATION**

# September 2005 – October

## M.Eng. in Computer Engineering & Informatics (5 year Diploma)

2010 University of Patras, Patras (Greece)

S/W Programming, H/W Programming, Computer Science

Diploma thesis: "Bioinformatics: Tools used for protein homology modelling."

Designed a website that guided the user through the process of creating a protein model by homology using Bioinformatics tools.

# September 2011 – August 2012

# **MSc in Bioinformatics**

University of Edinburgh, Edinburgh (United Kingdom)

Next Generation Sequencing, Bioinformatics Tools, Biological Data Analysis, R (Statistical Computing), Perl for Bioinformatics

Master thesis: "Finding New Drug Targets"

Designed and implemented a full web site/tool that extracts information from different high throughput data sets measured for budding yeast into a database. The combined data were analysed in order to determine characteristics of the different genes, in particular the characteristics of genes involved in responses to stress. Such genes may make ideal drug targets because they are activated by the pathogenic yeast, Candida albicans, when it invades a human host.

8/12/16 Page 2 / 3

# Tania Papazafeiropoulou - Curriculum vitae

## PERSONAL SKILLS

#### Mother language

Greek

Other	languages

**UNDERSTANDING SPEAKING** WRITING Listening Reading Spoken interaction Spoken production C1 C2 C1 C1 C1 A2 В1 **A**1 **A**1 **A**1 A2 B2 **A**1 **A**1 A2

English French Ancient Greek

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user - B1 and B2: Independent user - C1 and C2: Proficient user Common European Framework of Reference for Languages

**Technologies** 

Software Programming (Node.js, AngularJS, HTML5, Javascript, jQuery, Ajax, Sass/Scss, Css3, MySQL, MS SQL, Coldfusion, PHP, C, C++, C#, Java, VBA, Perl, Python, R and Matlab, XML / XSL).

Hardware Programming (including Arduino) and Theoretical Computing.

Other Interests

When not playing with new technologies or working on fun little projects, in my free time I usually practice singing with my band or go dancing with my friends. For more relaxing times, I enjoy reading a good book.

Also, I love swimming and water sports.

I studied piano for 9 years. Additionally, I took theory of music, solfège, dictée and harmony lessons and was a choir member. Also, I took ballet dancing and painting lessons.

8/12/16 Page 3 / 3